plusonespro.com 2013-11-15

# PlusOnesPro

First and foremost, LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro are here to offer a good and honest service to those who want primarily to grow their reach on Twitter, Google+ and Youtube. We ask that you use the service fairly and honestly too. This Policy applies as to all products and services provided by LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro Truejay the owner and provider of LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro, and yourself the User of LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro. This Policy applies to our use of any and all Data collected by us in relation to your use of LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro and any Services or Systems therein. Please read the Liking carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we treat it.

##### 1\. Definitions & interpretations

The Liking terms shall have the Liking meanings:

â€œ **Account** â€ means collectively the personal information, payment information and credentials used by Users to access material and/or any communications System on LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro

â€œ **Content** â€ means any text, graphics, images, audio, video, software, data compilations and any other form of information capable of being stored in a computer that appears on or forms part of LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro

â€œ **Cookie** â€ means a small text file placed on your computer by LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro when you visit certain parts of the Website. This allows us to identify recurring visitors and to analyze their browsing habits within LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro

â€œ **Data** â€ means collectively all information that you submit to the Website. This includes, but is not limited to, Account details and information submitted using any of our Services or Systems

â€œ **LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro** â€/â€œ **LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro** â€ (â€˜Weâ€™/â€˜Usâ€™/â€˜Truejayâ€™) means the Website and Truejay, Inc. located at 5795 S. Sandhill Road Suite F Las Vegas, Nevada 89120

â€œ **Service** â€/â€œ **Services** â€ means collectively any online facilities, tools, services or information that Truejay makes available through LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro either now or in the future

â€œ **System** â€ means any online communications infrastructure that LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro makes available through LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro either now or in the future. This includes, but is not limited to, web-based email, message boards, live chat facilities and email links

â€œ **User** â€/â€œ **Users** â€ means any third party that accesses LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro and is not employed by LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro and acting in the course of their employment

â€œ **Website** â€ means the website that you are currently using (LikesPro.com, PlusOnesPro.com, FollowsPro.com, RetweetsPro.com) and any sub-domains of this site (e.g. support.likespro.com unless expressly excluded)

â€œ **Truejay** â€ means Truejay, Inc. the owner of LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro, the Website, and the provider of the Services.

##### 2\. Protecting your privacy

We use the latest technologies and processes to ensure that any information (personal data) that you supply us is kept secure at all times.

This policy (together with our Terms and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.

##### 3\. Information collected from you

This is the information you provide by filling in forms on [LikesPro.com](http://likespro.com/), [PlusOnesPro.com](http://plusonespro.com/), [FollowsPro.com](http://followspro.com/), [RetweetsPro.com](http://retweetspro.com/) (our site). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. This may include; your name; date of birth; gender; business industry; contact information such as email addresses and telephone numbers; demographic information such as post code, preferences and interests; website profile information.

3.1 We may also ask you for information when you enter a competition or promotion sponsored by Truejay, and when you report a problem with our site.

3.2 We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.

3.3 If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

3.4 Details of transactions you carry out through our site including purchase history and of the fulfillment of your orders.

3.5 Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

3.6 Details of your use of our services, including the online social connections made or received by you through LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro.

3.7 Twitter profile information provided to us through the Twitter API with your express permission.

3.8 Other automatically collected information will include; web browser type and version; operating system; a list of URLS starting with a referring site, your activity on LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro, and the site you exit to.

##### 4\. Your IP address

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

##### 5\. Cookies

We may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on your browser or the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalized service. Some of the cookies we use are essential for the site to operate. If you register with us or if you continue to use our site, you agree to our use of cookies. Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.

##### 6\. How your data is stored

##### Staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfillment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be handled by PayPal and encrypted using SSL technology. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.

##### 7\. How we use your information

We use information held about you in the Liking ways:

7.1 To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.

7.2 To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.

7.3 To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.

7.4 To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to.

7.5 To notify you about changes to our service.

##### 8\. Third party websites & services

We may use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you.

If you are an existing member, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.

If you are a new member, and where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this.

LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro may, from time to time, employ the services of other parties for dealing with matters that may include, but are not limited to, payment handling, delivery of purchased items, search engine facilities, advertising and marketing. The providers of such services do have access to certain personal Data provided by Users of LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro. Any Data used by such parties is used only to the extent required by them to perform the services that LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro requests. Any use for other purposes is strictly prohibited. Furthermore, any Data that is processed by third parties must be processed within the terms of this Policy.

If you do not want us to use your data in this way, please email a request to remove your information from our records to info@plusonespro.com

##### 9\. Disclosure of your information

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries.

The reasons we may disclose your personal information are:

9.1 In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

9.2 If Xferral or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its members will be one of the transferred assets.

9.3 If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use.

##### 10\. Your rights

You may access certain areas of LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro without providing any Data at all. However, to use all Services and Systems available on LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro you may be required to submit Account information or other Data.

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at info@plusonespro.com

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you Like a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

You have the right to opt out of receiving information from LikesPro, PlusOnesPro, FollowsPro, RetweetsPro at any time. You can turn-off notifications on the settings page if you don't want to receive system notifications.

You have the right to delete your account by emailing us at info@socialmarketingincubator.com

##### 11\. Changes to our policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

##### 12\. Contact us

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to info@plusonespro.com

### Our Pro Sites

Get thousands of Google +1s.

Get thousands of Twitter followers.

Get thousands of Twitter retweets.

Get thousands of Facebook / Youtube views and likes.

### Our Sister Site

Get feedback on just about anything.
